

Almir Hrštić

O Home: 38173, Sickte, Germany

Email: <u>almirhrstic@gmail.com</u> **@ Website:** <u>almir-hrstic.github.io/portfolio</u>

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/almir-hrstic

Gender: Male **Date of birth:** 26/03/1995 **Nationality:** Bosnian-Herzegovinian

ABOUT ME

I officially began my journey in late 2016 when I enrolled in a technical university, acquiring theoretical knowledge. Meanwhile, I embarked on a student internship, which provided me with practical experience. Later, I transitioned into full-time work, taking on numerous responsibilities. I am now exploring new opportunities, with a focus on frontend development and e-commerce.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[09/2010 - 05/2014]

Technician of Electrical Engineering

Co-educational High School "Hasan Kikić", High School of Electrical **Engineering** msshkg.co.ba

Citv: Gradačac

[09/2016 - 05/2020]

Bachelor Engineer of Information Technology

American University in Bosnia and Herzegovina, Faculty of Information **Technology** aubih.edu

City: Tuzla

WORK EXPERIENCE

[09/2018 - 05/2019]

Front-end Developer

StarNet starnet.co.ba

City: Tuzla

Student internship, part-time and in a remote environment. Integrated segments of a chosen Bootstrap theme using the Aurelia framework for enhanced reusability.

[09/2019 - 05/2020]

Full-stack Developer

Leftor leftor.com

City: Tuzla

Student internship, part-time and in a hybrid environment. Established IMS and CAS as in-house solutions using React, Bootstrap and Laravel frameworks.

[09/2020 - 08/2023] **WordPress Developer**

Imel <u>imel.ba</u>

City: Lukavac

Full-time and in a hybrid (largely remote) environment. Developed and maintained custom-tailored e-commerce and other solutions using the WordPress platform.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Bosnian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

German

LISTENING A1 READING A1 WRITING A1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION A1 SPOKEN INTERACTION A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user